



SKILLS

HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS

JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Express.js.

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

Accessibility, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Material-UI, Next.js, React.js, Redux, SCSS, TypeScript.

BACK-END DEVELOPMENT

Express.js, Firebase, Node.js, REST API.

DATABASE MANAGEMENT

MongoDB, SQLite.

TESTING

Jest.

OTHER Git.

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Finnish - Novice

Vietnamese - Native

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

React - The Complete Guide -Udemy (December 2021).

CCNA R&S: Routing and Switching Essentials - Cisco Networking Academy (April 2020).

CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Networks - Cisco Networking Academy (April 2018).

KIM NGUYEN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Kokkola, Finland

Kim is an accomplished Full Stack Developer with a proven track record, both within the Software Development and Design industry. His skill set goes beyond the Information Technology sector as he has gained experience in communication and coordination while working as a Front-End Developer. Moreover, Kim has a high attention to detail and is not afraid to unleash his creative side, especially during his employment as a Sound and Visual Designer. All in all, Kim has proven himself to have a multitude of skills, and is a strong asset to all software development companies.

RECENT PROJECTS

React E-Commerce Template

React.js

A project built in order to strengthen and showcase professional abilities in building modern e-commerce platforms.

Restaurant Website

React.is

A functional website built for a local restaurant, which improved the ability to work with the end-users.

Travelogue

React.js

A website built for an end-customer, a tourism agency named Travelogue. This website was built as a part of a Bachelor's thesis.

Portfolio

Next.js, Styled Components

A professional portfolio for showcasing expertise as a software developer.

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | January 2022 - Present

- · Sharpening competence as a Full Stack Developer by collaborating with other developers of different seniorities on a diverse range of projects and real-life challenaes.
- · Focusing on front-end development with JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Redux in addition to other technologies and concepts such as accessibility and animations.
- · Building back-end for web-based applications with frameworks such as Node.js and Express.js.
- · Covering additional concepts such as API development and documentation, unit testing with Jest, SQL and NoSQL databases, and version control with GitHub.
- · Working with DevOps practices (Bash scripting, Docker containers, and CI/CD with GitHub Actions) and Cloud Services with AWS.

SOUND AND VISUAL DESIGNER

CENTRIAxECC game | Kokkola, Finland | March 2021

- · Cooperated with graduates students from the ECC Computer College in Osaka, Japan to develop a video game.
- · Designed numerous aspects of 2D game environments such as animations, characters, and sound effects.

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

DUDE do unlimited | Kokkola, Finland | June 2020 - December 2020

- · Designed and developed a tourism application for the city of Kalajoki, Oulu.
- · Coordinated teamwork with other graduate students at the Centria University of Applied Sciences and Kpedu from other fields.
- · Technologies used: Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js and React.js.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Centria Summer Workshop | Kokkola, Finland | May 2019 - August 2019

- · Collaborated with other graduate students at the Centria University of Applied Sciences to design and build a mobile application for advertisers.
- Developed a front-end prototype for the mobile application
- $\cdot \, {\sf Technologies} \, {\sf used: Cordova, JavaScript, Raspberry \, Pi, and \, Ruuvitag \, Bluetooth}$ beacons.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

University of Lodz | Lodz, Poland | August 2019

- · Designed and developed a mobile application for universities in collaboration with other developers.
- · Coordinated team efforts of graduate students from Poland, Belgium, Ireland, Portugal, France, Slovenia, and Ukraine. Technologies used: Cordova, JavaScript, and Pvthon.
- This experience is a part of the GGULIVRR Lodz 2019 project.

EDUCATION

B. SC. IN INFORMATION AND TECHNOLOGY

Centria University of Applied Sciences | Kokkola, Finland | February 2017 - September

























